Hey everyone, thanks for listening to
the Grow Your Life podcast. My name is
Jeremiah Kowski. For those you I haven't
met yet, I've built multiple coaching
businesses to eight figures over the
last 22 years. And I'm here to help
coaches, course creators, and mentors
scale their businesses beyond their
wildest dreams. Today, I'm going to talk
about mindset. I'm talking about the
brain work. I'm going to talk about the
stuff that makes everything tick and
makes it all go together. I believe and
I know that strategy alone is not what's
going to produce the results for you but
it's about thinking in a way that's
going to allow you to implement the
strategy. Often times I meet people they
have been learning the strategies for 10
15 years and they still can't implement
them because of certain limitations in
their beliefs and mindset. Now, all I
can share with you today is my own
experiences, but I want to share with
you just some recent experiences that
have been really helping me a lot when
it comes to that mindset. Number one, I
want to mention there's actually a book
that I really enjoy reading. It's called
The Game of Life and How to Play It by
Florence Scoville Shin. Um, it's on
YouTube. You can go check it out. Highly
recommend it. And there's some concepts
in that that have really been helping me
a lot. One of the first is this is to
not have any animosity towards another
person. And we're going to dive right
into it right here. Can I tell you this
is that there is in our lives so much
energy that we put towards our thinking,
our stinking thinking that keeps us from
doing what we need to do. We need to
build our business, but our brain is
thinking about somebody who did us wrong
or did us dirty or hurt us. Now again,
we all have trauma, we all have pain, we
all things that have happened to us. But
if your ever consuming thought
is how upset you are about other
people's behavior, that is going to
limit you from being able to be able to
reach your goals in your business. So
number one, I know I'm challenging some
of you right here. You got to get rid of
that animosity, I think, towards other
people because we end up then being
energetically tied to those people. And
what I mean by that is not in some like
woo woo new age way, but rather our
energy is literally just going towards
this other person trying to resolve
something that is probably never going
to be resolved because we're focusing on
the wrong stuff. Focus on yourself.
Focus on what you can do and focus on
how you can adjust and change your life.
Now the other thing is this is that
often times we have to realize that the
life that we are experiencing we are
choosing and this is another toughy
because let's say that you don't like
what you're experiencing in your life
right now. What I want you to realize is
that you have one life and the life you
have right now is your life.
Everything that's going on in your life
right now, I want you to start choosing
it. Meaning, I have chosen this life and
I have chosen to do my very best to make
it the best life that's possible. No
matter what situation is going on right
now, what this does is this allows you
to take ownership over your present
situation to where you're not avoiding
looking at it. I was doing this myself
and gosh, it doesn't work at all. When
we are avoiding looking at our
situations, when we are avoiding shining
a light
on what's really going on beneath the
surface because we don't like certain
things that are going on. We're not
looking at certain things there. We're
avoiding talking about certain things.
We're avoiding taking a look at those
things. Could be related to your health,
could be related to your finances, could
be related to your
relationships. And those are kind of the
big three right there. that I think a
lot of times we avoid looking at out of
embarrassment or fear. And whatever you
avoid looking at is always going to
remain the same. Whatever you shine
focus on will start to improve. Now the
next part is having a vision for the
life that you want. And I'm not talking
about the kind of money you want to
make, but having a vision for the
experience of the life that you want to
where you can feel it before it starts
to happen. If you can feel it, you can
create
it. Every single thing that exists on
planet Earth right now was felt by
another person at some moment in time.
They saw it. They had a vision for it
and they created it. And you can do the
same exact thing yourself. The way that
you create in your life, in your
business, is by having a vision for that
life and business that you want. And
things eb and flow. Things change.
That's why going back to choosing your
life means you're also choosing the eb
and flow. Oftent times for us to grow
things are not going to be consistent.
We crave
consistency and from what I understand
uh I
think women crave consistency a bit more
than men do overall. I think men
sometimes are have a tendency to more
thrive in chaos a little bit more than
than women. I think that's just a just a
common thing that we all know. It's kind
of how we're wired. Um, but I've found
that often times consistent feels safe
and we crave it and we want to be
consistent. That's why we have routines.
But oftent times for us to grow to the
next level in our life, we have to shake
some things up. We're going to have to
be able to step into those uncomfortable
feelings. And that takes me to the next
part of what I wanted to share with you
is I want
you to feel three things. Number one,
confident. Number one, unstoppable. And
number three, number three. Number one,
number two, unstoppable. Number three,
fully
safe. And those three words, confident,
unstoppable, and safe. When you combine
those three
together, it's incredible.
I want you to take imagine right now
that you had all the support in the
world that you could ever
want. I want you to imagine that you
have
everything that you need to accomplish
every goal that you have. And maybe
you've never even thought about what
that would feel like. I want you to
start feeling that inside of your
nervous
system, the calm, the peace, meditating
on having all the support that you need,
having all the wisdom that you need,
knowing how to do everything that you
need to do. Even if in your present
reality doesn't feel that way, thinking
on these things is going to help you
start to solve problems. Today, we have
so much at our disposable with
artificial
intelligence to be able to solve
problems, to be able to answer
questions that we really do have all the
support that we need. And if you're in
my wealthy coach academy program and
you're a member of that, you have
support from me to work with me where
I'm going to show you exactly what to do
in your business and I'm going to come
alongside you to make sure that you
succeed. That's my mission. That's why I
do what I do. That's how I help people
every single day is inside of that
wealthy coach academy
program. So the process that I want to
take you through is
this. I want you to imagine two things.
Number one, I believe in God and I
believe that we are all carriers of
divine energy.
We are carriers of God's essence, God's
presence. And
so what ends up happening though is
sometimes we forget that. I have I can
forget it for months on
end. Total vulnerable moment here when
my wife gave birth. The moment where I
needed to be carrier a carrier of God's
presence. I feel like I walked away from
that just a little bit and tried to do
it all in my own strength and everything
in my life started to suffer because of
it. Now I'm like, okay, I get it
now. And it's about what are we filling
ourselves up with, too? It's a big part
of that. What messages are we filling
ourselves up with? But I want you to
always remember, you got to do these two
things. And this is this is going to
lead you to breakthrough in your
mindset. Remember who you
are from the perspective of how God sees
you.
Okay. And again, maybe you call it Holy
Spirit or source or something like that.
Okay. Higher power. I believe in God and
I believe
that I also do believe though
that it works if you believe in
something. So, I know that. But what
I've chosen is is is Jesus, the God of
the Bible.
And so with that, I find
that believing that I'm a carrier of his
presence everywhere that I go. That's
not in a pompous, arrogant way, like I'm
better than everybody because I I got
God in me and I am God manifesting,
right? But like I can have the
unstoppable, unshakable confidence that
I am a carrier of God's
presence and that's huge. Okay. Now
number
two is feelings of safety. Feeling that
I am
safe to walk that out and that I am safe
to feel the hard things in my
life. That I am safe to go into scary
situations and do tough stuff. And I'll
tell you, when you combine these two
things together, being the carrier of a
divine
presence, combined with total absolute
belief in your safety in all situations,
when it comes to your business, when it
comes to your
life. Now, of course, we use wisdom. You
know, I'm not going to
go put myself into situations that are
physically dangerous for me. But I'll
tell you this, I got friends
who have done that and and I'll tell
you, they inspire me. Their stories. I
got my friend Georgian Banoff. He
actually went down,
ministered, played music, hung out with
families at the border of Israel and
Gaza. I mean, like
what scary place, right? I I don't want
to be there right now. That's a scary
place. And gosh, it's so hard on both
sides of that. But he was able to go and
and love on the people down there
because that's that's really I think
what God's spirit is is loving on
people. And
so, he's one of the most confident,
fearless people that I know. I mean,
gosh, I'm so I'm glad I'm be be a friend
with him. So, I'm glad that he's one of
my friends.
But in that, like he was telling me that
story and I'm like,
man, I get
it. Because he felt safe in that moment
to go do something that terrifies most
people. And that's what allows us to
accomplish great things is we feel
absolute
safety to do the tough stuff. And
oftentimes it it comes from that
realizing that you are not separate from
God. That God is in you and a part of
you and that you are a part of part of
him, part of
God. And believing
that and
then telling yourself I am safe and
believing that you are safe. Even if a
situation is causing you anxiety,
telling yourself I'm safe to feel this
anxiety. It's okay. It's not going to
cause me the problems it has in the
past. And I'm okay to move forward in
the situation because I have all the
support that I need from heaven and here
on earth. And when you can tell yourself
that, you become unstoppable,
unshakable, confident, and safe to do
incredible things. And then what ends up
happening is a lot of our
procrastination that we've been dealing
with, a lot of the things that we've
been putting off in our life, we're no
longer putting them off because we feel
safe to go do them because we feel
inspired to go do them. certain thing
I'll tell you when I like tapped into
this what I just shared with you the
combination of okay God's presence and
safety to fully feel what's going on
inside of me to be able to go into
situations that maybe previously scared
me or made me take take some pause and
might be
afraid as soon as I started telling
myself I'm
safe and that I'm walking ing in my
divine creation from
heaven. I literally started getting
inspired to do certain things and and I
started seeing things even come together
in my life. Prayers started to become
answered that I felt like were never
going to be
answered. Hope started feeling like a
superpower because every time I would
hope for something, it would start to
happen. And it came from that place of I
okay I feel safe to receive those
things. Now yeah you got to go to work
but the work becomes easy. The work
becomes fun. The drudgery of doing the
work no longer feels like a
dread. And it's something that we can
all
do. So that's what I just want to
encourage you is remember those
things. I love some of Dr. Joe Despenses
Joe Despensza's teaching on this is he
talks about this is that if you
can no longer see yourself as separate
from God or he calls it
source and you become no longer a person
you're no longer attached to time you're
no longer in a space like in your mind
you visualize yourself that you are just
always is, was, has been
divine. You end up then tapping into
what's in quantum physics and it
literally can shift
atmospheres, the world around you. You
are literally shaping the world around
you through
that. And I never understood how that
would happen. There is actually proven
science behind this that we influence
the spaces and the world around us by
how we walk, operate and believe and
live from that place.
That's what a lot of his teaching is
about is being able to not just
visualize, but then also how do we shift
things in our
lives. I believe that no matter what
situation you're in right now,
relationally, financially, you can shift
things. You might need to relisten to
this episode again. I think there's a
lot of nuggets in here that'll help you.
I've given you a couple of different
resources. I mentioned at the beginning
the book how the game of life and how to
play it by Francis Goville Shin
life-changing book and then some of Dr.
Joe Despensza's videos like those are a
great place to start on YouTube to maybe
do this journey for
yourself. I believe that you can live an
incredible life greater than you've ever
imagined and I'd love to see the results
of that. I'd love to have you in my
Wealthy Coach Academy program where we
are helping mentors and coaches become
the wealthiest that they possibly could
become and you could be next. Grow your
life everybody and we'll talk soon. Have
a good one.
[Applause]
[Music]